Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy. UARC.0401
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Campus Theatre Board, Development of., 1940-1953.; 1 bound volume (Box 52)
  Index code 38-C.
- Chancellor's Office., 1960-1970. (Box 52)
- Community Service Committee., 1960-1962. (Box 52)
  Index code 38-CS.
- Fine Arts Production Committee., 1963-1964. (Box 52)
  Index code 38-FA.
- Chancellor's Planning Committee., 1959-1960. (Box 53)
  Index code 39-Plan.
- Charles E. Young. Kudos., 1968. (Box 53)
  Index code 39-CEY.
- Charles E. Young. Personal File., 1961-1963; 1965-1969. (Box 53)
- C. Z. Wilson., 1969-1970. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-CZW.
- Charles E. Young. Appointment to Chancellor., 1968-1970. (Box 54)
- David S. Saxon., 1969-1970. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-DSS.
- Elwin V. Svenson., 1970. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-EVS.
- Franklin D. Murphy., 1964-1965. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-FDM.
- Institutional Studies at UCLA., 1966. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-IS.
- James W. Hobson., 1968-1970. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-JWH.
- Robert S. Kinsman., 1970. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-RSK.
- William G. Young., 1961-1968. (Box 54)
  Index code 39-WGY.
- Kinescope Film Library., 1955-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 55)
  Index code 41-TV.
- Miss Frederickson., 1962. (Box 55)
  Index code 40.
- Public Information Office., 1960-1970. (Box 55)
  Index code 41.
- Purchasing Department., 1960-1963. (Box 55)
  Index code 42.
- Television., 1960-1961. (Box 55)
- William G. Young. Preistley Award Correspondence., 1967-1968. (Box 55)
- Purchasing Department., 1964-1970. (Box 56)
- Registrar., 1958-1970. (Box 56)
  Index code 43.
- Committee on Year-Round Operation Chancellor's Committee/Task Force., 1963-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 57)
  Index code 45.
- Enrollments and Estimates., 1958-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 57)
- Higher Education., 1965-1969. (Box 57)
  Index code 44.
- Registrar. Development of On-Line Enrollment., 1967-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 57)
  Index code 43
- Summer Session., 1960-1970. (Box 57)
- Year Round Use of University Facilities (Tri-mester Plan)., 1959-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 57)
- Educational Placement Office., 1964. (Box 58)
  Index code 46.
- Placement Center., 1965-1969. (Box 58)
- Student Health Service., 1961-1968. (Box 58)
  Index code 48.
- Telephone, Telegraph, Teletype., 1960-1970. (Box 58)
  Index code 47.
- Year Round Use of University Facilities (Tri-mester Plan), 1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 58)
- Hospital and Clinics., 1953-1968. (Box 59)
  Index code 49.
- Hospital and Medical Center., 1960-1966. (Box 59)
- Student Health Service., 1969-1970. (Box 59)
- Cresap, McCormick, and Paget Report on Organization, Administration and Management of UCLA Hospital., 1964-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 60)
- Hospital and Clinics., 1969-1970. (Box 60)
- Professional Fees for Insured Patients., 1959-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 60)
- Employee Medical Facility, Establishment of., 1963-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 61)
- Harbor General Hospital., 1957-1960. (Box 61)
  Index code 49-HGH.
- Health Sciences Computing Facility., 1967-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 61)
  Index code 49.45.
- Inpatient Agreement and Emergency Aid Plan., 1960-1962. (Box 61)
  Index code 49-A.
- Western Data Processing Center., 1960-1967. (Box 61)
  Index code 51.
- Wilson, Hazel Eckhart, Pavilion., 1964-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 61)
  Index code 49-W.
- Acquisitions (Campus Computing Network)., 1970. (Box 62)
  Index code 51.1
- Acquisitions (Campus Computing Network). 360/91., 1965-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 62)
  Index code 51.1.
- Gerald Shure Project., 1969. (Box 62)
- Western Data Processing Center., 1968-1970. (Box 62)
- Acquisitions (Campus Computing Network). 360/91., 1968-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 63)
- Acquisitions (Campus Computing Network). 360/75., 1968-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 63)
- Acquisitions (Campus Computing Network). 360/30-40., 1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 63)
- Acquisitions (Campus Computing Network). 360/50., 1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 63)
- Acquisitions (Campus Computing Network). 360/44-G., 1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 63)
- Alumni Matters., 1959-1970. (Box 63)
  Index code 56.
- Chancellor's Staff., 1968. (Box 63)
  Index code 54.
- Complaints on Service., 1970. (Box 63)
  Index code 51.9.
- Estates and Dead Donors., 1969-1970. (Box 63)
  Index code 56.95.
- Health Sciences Computing Facility., 1963-1969. (Box 63)
  Index code 53.
- Policy on Use., 1970. (Box 63)
  Index code 51.3.
- Rates, Billing., 1970. (Box 63)
  Index code 51.7.
- Scholarships., 1965-1969. (Box 63)
  Index code 63.
- Storehouse., 1969. (Box 63)
  Index code 55.
- UCLA Computing Facilities., 1960-1969. (Box 63)
  Index code 52.
- Western Data Processing Center., 1960-1969. (Box 63)
- Aliens., 1960-1970. (Box 64)
  Index code 58.
- Catalina Marine Science Center., 1967-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 64)
  Index code 60.
- Fees. Other Than Incidental Fees., 1960-1970. (Box 64)
  Index code 66.
- Fellowships (Faculty-TA-RA)., 1965-1970. (Box 64)
  Index code 64.
- Jury Duty Exemptions., 1961-1970. (Box 64)
  Index code 57.
- Legal Matters., 1970. (Box 64)
  Index code 62.
- Loans., 1965-1969. (Box 64)
  Index code 65.
- Natural Resources., 1965-1970. (Box 64)
- NDEA. Title II. National Defense Education Act., 1964-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 64)
- Printing and Publishing., 1965-1969. (Box 64)
  Index code 59.
- Chancellor's Advisory Committee on the Use of the Incidental Fee., 1965-1969. (Box 65)
  Index code 66-C.
- Fees. Other Than Incidental Fees., 1959-1970. (Box 65)
- Graduate Student Association Fee (Berkeley and Statewide)., 1954-1965.; 1 bound volume (Box 65)
  Index code 66-G.
- Incidental Fee. Levy and Allocation., 1960-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 65)
  Index code 66-F.
- Uses of the Incidental Fee at UCLA., 1960-1968. (Box 65)
  Index code 66-U.
- Waivers (Tuition Fee Waivers)., 1960-1970. (Box 65)
- Belt, Elmer, Library., 1961-1964. (Box 66)
  Index code 67-B.
- Bond, Carrie Jacobs, Memorial., 1944-1962. (Box 66)
- Gifts and Donations., 1960-1969. (Box 66)
  Includes: memos, correspondence, policies regarding the administration of gifts to UCLA; includes the establishment of the Gifts and Endowment Office in 1960.
  Index code 67.
- Individual Gifts., 1967. (Box 66)
  Alphabetical by letter.
  Index code 67-A.
- Paintings, Sale of (Original Gift from Marion Davies to Pediatrics)., 1957-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 66)
- Boodin, John E., Estate of., 1947-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 67)
- Connell, Michael J., Fund., 1940-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 67)
  Index code 67-C.
- Goldwyn, Samuel. Center for Postrgraduate Studies., 1965-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 67)
  Index code 67-G.
- Hollywood Center Foundation., 1956-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 67)
  Index code 67-H.
- Insurance., 1961-1965. (Box 67)
  Index code 68.
- Kennedy Collection. Art Galleries., 1954-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 67)
  Index code 67-K.
- Neutra, Richard J., Gift., 1955-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 67)
  Index code 67-N.
- Norton, Edith A., Fund., 1948-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 67)
  Index code 67-N, 67-R, and 67-S.
- Accident Reports., 1963. (Box 68)
  Index code 68-AR.
- Auto Permits., 1961. (Box 68)
  Index code 68-AP.
- Equipment., 1966-1969. (Box 68)
  Index code 69.
- Injury Reports., 1961-1963. (Box 68)
  Index code 68-I.
- Insurance, Employee., 1970. (Box 68)
  Index code 68.5.
- Insurance, Malpractice., 1961-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 68)
- Insurance., 1967-1970. (Box 68)
- Real Estate., 1960-1962. (Box 68)
  Index code 71.
- Retirement., 1965-1970. (Box 68)
  Index code 70.
- Use of the Athletic Field., 1947-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 68)
- Real Estate., 1963-1969. (Box 69)
- Retirement Matters., 1961-1969. (Box 69)
  Index code 72.
- Transferring Members of the Pension and Retiring Annuities Systems to the State Employees Retirement System., 1951-1954.; 1 bound volume (Box 69)
- Japanese Gardens. Use of University Facilities., 1965-1970. (Box 70)
  Index code 85.
- Physical Plant., 1965-1970. (Box 70)
  Index code 81.
- Safety., 1953-1960. (Box 70)
  Index code 87.
- Track and Field Facility., 1965-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 70)
  Index code 84.
- Transportation Problems., 1962-1963. (Box 70)
  Index code 74.
- Travel., 1960-1969. (Box 70)
  Index code 73.
- Use and Misuse of Buildings and Facilities., 1962-1970. (Box 70)
  Index code 86.
- Animal Care Committees and Their Relation to Medical and Non-Medical Vivariums., 1939-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 71)
  Index code 87-S.
- Buildings. General., 1960-1970. (Box 71)
  Index code 88.
- Disaster Preparedness., 1961-1963. (Box 71)
  Index code 87-D.
- Safety, 1962-1970. (Box 71)
- Self-Contained Underwater Breathing Apparatus., 1953-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 71)
  Index code 87-SCUBA.
- Traffic Signals., 1957-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 71)
  Index code 87-T.
- Various Buildings., 1954-1970. (Box 71)
- Buildings, Committee to Consider Naming of., 1950-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 72)
- Dickson Art Center/Dickson Court., 1956-1963. (Box 72)
  Index code 88-Art.
- Dormitories. (Dykstra, Rieber, Sproul Halls)., 1958-1964. (Box 72)
  Index code 88-Dorm.
- Engineering Field Station, Possible Off-Campus Sites for., 1951-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 72)
  Index code 88-Engin.
- Faculty Center., 1962-1964. (Box 72)
  Index code 88-Fac.
- Master Plan of the Campus., 1957-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 72)
- Streets and Roads, Campus Committee to Consider Naming of., 1940-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 72)
- University Activities Memorial Center (Multi-Purpose Pavilion)., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 72)
  Index code 88-Field.
- Cardiovascular Research Laboratory., 1952-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Med.
- Graduate Business., 1954-1969. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Grad.
- Hershey Residence Hall., 1963-1966. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-MMH.
- Kerckhoff Hall., 1963-1970. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Kerck.
- Law Building., 1961. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Law.
- Library Building., 1949-1960. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Lib.
- Library. North Campus #1., 1960-1969. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Lib No. 1.
- Murphy Hall Administration Building., 1964-1970. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-M.
- Music Building. Schoenberg Hall., 1955-1962. (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Music.
- Neuropsychiatric Institute (Mental Hygiene)., 1951-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Neuro.
- Rehabilitation Center., 1958-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 73)
  Index code 88-Med Rehab.
- 1970-75 Capital Improvement Program and Proposition Three Bond Issue., 1969-1970. (Box 74)
  Index code 88.25.
- Child Care Day Nursery Center., 1969-1970. (Box 74)
  Index code 88.5.
- Nuclear Medicine and Radiation Biology Laboratory., 1958-1964. (Box 74)
  Index code 88-Nuc.
- Parking., 1959-1960. (Box 74)
  Index code 90.
- Physics Building., 1960-1964. (Box 74)
  Index code 88-Phycs.
- Plant Science Building., 1953; 1960. (Box 74)
  Index code 88-PlantSci.
- Royce Hall Alterations., 1968-1970. (Box 74)
  Index code 88.5R.
- Space Assignments., 1960-1970. (Box 74)
  Index code 88-Space.
- Student Union., 1960-1967. (Box 74)
  Index code 88-SU.
- Theater Arts Building., 1963-1969. (Box 74)
  Index code 88-TA.
- University Memorial Activities Center., 1961-1964. (Box 74)
  Index code 88-UMAC.
- University Memorial Activities Center (Multi-Purpose Pavilion)., 1962-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 74)
- Courtesy Parking Permits., 1961. (Box 75)
  Index code 90-P.
- Financial Aids Office., 1967-1969. (Box 75)
  Index code 92.
- Parking Fees., 1959-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 75)
- Parking., 1961-1970. (Box 75)
- Tree Planting, Removal., 1958-1963. (Box 75)
  Index code 90-T.
- Vivarium., 1960-1970. (Box 75)
  Index code 91.
- Faculty Recruitment., 1965-1969. (Box 76)
  Index code 94.
- Research Contracts. Contracts and Grants., 1960-1965. (Box 76)
  Index code 96.
- Research., 1960-1970. (Box 76)
  Index code 95.
- Surveys., 1964-1967; 1970. (Box 76)
  Includes report on Mexican American Studies Project/MASP submitted by Leo Grebler (1965 December).
  Index code 93.
- Atomic Energy Commission., 1960. (Box 77)
  Index code 96-AEC.
- Defense Department. Army, Navy, Air Force., 1970. (Box 77)
  Index code 96.22.
- Health, Education, and Welfare (HEW)., 1970. (Box 77)
  Index code 96.25.
- National Institutes of Health (NIH)., 1970. (Box 77)
- National Science Foundation (NSF)., 1970. (Box 77)
  Index code 96.28.
- National Science Foundation., 1960. (Box 77)
  Index code 96-NatlSci.
- Navy., 1960. (Box 77)
  Index code 96-N.
- Private Foundation Grants., 1970. (Box 77)
  Index code 96.8.
- Research Contracts. Contracts and Grants., 1966-1970. (Box 77)
- State Granting Agencies., 1970. (Box 77)
  Index code 96.6.
- U.S. Federal Granting Agencies., 1970. (Box 77)
  Index code 96.2.
- Doris Duke American History Project., 1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 78)
- Faculty Intercampus Transfers., 1965-1970. (Box 78)
  Index code 99.
- Nepotism., 1969. (Box 78)
  Index code 98.
- Patent and Copyright Policies., 1960; 1963-1970. (Box 78)
  Index code 97.
- University Policy and Regulation., 1965-1970. (Box 78)
  Index code 100.
- Class Lecture Notes., 1963-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 79)
- Task Force on the Extended University., 1970. (Box 79)
  Index code 101.
- University Rules and Regulations Regarding Student Activities, Etc., 1964-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 79)
- Universitywide., 1965-1970. (Box 79)
- Irvine Campus., 1968-1970. (Box 80)
  Index code 104.
- San Diego Campus., 1966-1970. (Box 80)
  Index code 102.
- Santa Cruz Campus., 1969. (Box 80)
  Index code 103.
- Task Force on Student Participation in Campus Governance., 1969-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 80)
- Task Groups. Faculty Ethics/Responsibility., 1970. (Box 80)
- UCLA - L.A. Campus., 1959-1970. (Box 80)
  Index code 105.
- Universitywide Growth Plan., 1969-1970. (Box 80)
- UCLA Chancellor's Arrowhead Conference., 1961-1968. (Box 81)
  Includes the following conference dates: January 1961; January 1962; January 1963; Sepember 1963; January 1965; January 1966, March and April 1967; March 1968; and November 1968.
- Berkeley Campus and Statewide., 1960-1970. (Box 82)
  Index code 106.
- Free Speech Movement., 1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 82)
  Index code 106-FSM.
- InAuguration of C. E. Young and 50th Anniversary of the University., 1967-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 82)
- Los Angeles Campus. Goals Committee., 1969-1970. (Box 82)
  Index code 105.5.
- New Campuses of the University., 1957-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 82)
- Riverside Campus., 1962-1963. (Box 83)
  Index code 108.
- Santa Barbara Campus., 1962-1964. (Box 83)
  Index code 107.
- University Regulations and Policies. Affiliation of Volunteer Groups with the University Use of University Name for Fund-Raising Privileges., 1954-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 83)
  Index code 106R.
- University Regulations and Policies. Fingerprinting of Employees., 1954-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 83)
- University Regulations and Policies. Medical Center Auxiliary., 1954-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 83)
- University Regulations and Policies. Smoking in Classrooms., 1947-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 83)
- University Regulations and Policies., 1957-1965. (Box 83)
- American Council on Education., 1966-1970. (Box 84)
  Index code 112.
- Davis Campus., 1961-1969. (Box 84)
  Index code 110.
- Environmental Studies and Research., 1954; 1969-1970. (Box 84)
  Index code 111.
- La Jolla Campus., 1961-1965. (Box 84)
  Index code 109.
- Atomic Energy Commission (AEC)., 1965-1970. (Box 85)
  Index code 118.
- California State Employees Association (CSEA)., 1960-1969. (Box 85)
  Index code 122.
- Community Service., 1965-1970. (Box 85)
  Index code 123.
- Cyclotron Building. Agreement with Atomic Energy Commission for Space and Equipment for., 1966-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 85)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare., 1969-1970. (Box 85)
  Index code 115.
- International Education, Institute of., 1969-1970. (Box 85)
  Index code 113.
- Marion Davies Foundation., 1957-1960; 1966-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 85)
- National Science Foundation (NSF)., 1963-1970. (Box 85)
  Index code 116.
- UCLA Art Council., 1965. (Box 85)
  Index code 121.
- Haynes Foundation, John Randolph and Dora., 1954-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 86)
- Legislative Matters. Federal., 1969-1970. (Box 86)
  Index code 127.
- Legislative Matters. State., 1960-1963. (Box 86)
  Index code 129.
- National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges., 1959-1970. (Box 86)
  Index code 128.
- University Sponsorships (Programs)., 1965-1969. (Box 86)
  Index code 124.
- Legislative Matters. State., 1961-1970. (Box 87)
- DICER Legislative Matters., 1970. (Box 88)
- DICER. UCLA DICER Program., 1970. (Box 88)
- Federal Relations Advisory Committee (FRAC)., 1970. (Box 88)
- Legislative Matters, State. Health Sciences Bond Issue. Proposition I., 1970. (Box 88)
- Proposition 1A., 1962. (Box 88)
  Index code 129P.
- Alcoholic Beverages, Use of., 1963-1970. (Box 89)
  Index code 131.
- Business. Office of Vice President., 1963-1970. (Box 89)
- Los Angeles County Elected Representatives, Public Officials, and Community Leaders., 1970. (Box 89)
- Los Angeles County Supervisors and Councilmen Appointments. Addresses and Phone Numbers., 1970. (Box 89)
- Proposition 1A., 1962. (Box 89)
- University Attorney., 1965-1970. (Box 89)
  Index code 130.
- Education Abroad., 1965-1969. (Box 90)
  Index code 136.
- Religious Conference. Project India., 1958-1962. (Box 90)
  Index code 135.
- Religious Matters., 1960-1963. (Box 90)
- Rockefeller Foundation., 1963. (Box 90)
  Index code 138.
- Sunset Canyon Recreation Center., 1962-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 90)
  Index code 134.
- Taxes., 1965-1970. (Box 90)
  Index code 132.
- Teaching., 1965-1970. (Box 90)
  Index code 133.
- The Affiliates., 1965. (Box 90)
  Index code 137.
- Accreditation., 1957-1970. (Box 91)
  Index code 139.
- California College of Medicine., 1965-1967. (Box 91)
  Index code 142.
- Philippine-English Teaching Grant. Rockefeller Foundation., 1956-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 91)
- Relations With Other Universities., 1965-1968. (Box 91)
  Index code 140.
- Special Education Programs., 1965-1967. (Box 91)
  Index code 143.
- Agency for International Development., 1965-1970. (Box 92)
  Index code 145.
- Ford Foundation., 1960-1964; 1966-1970. (Box 92)
  Index code 146.
- Ford Foundation. Research., 1965-1969. (Box 92)
  Index code 146-Res.
- Fund for the Advancement of Education., 1958. (Box 92)
  Index code 146-Fund.
- HENAC., 1970. (Box 92)
- ILCA Latin American Study Center in Bogota., 1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 92)
- Special Education Programs., 1968-1969. (Box 92)
- University Committee on International Training and Research., 1964. (Box 92)
  Index code 146-U.
- Ethnic Arts and Technology - Museum and Laboratories, 1963-1970.; 3 folders. (Box 93)
  Index code 148.
- Laboratory of Nuclear Medicine and Radiation Biology., 1964-1969.; 2 folders. (Box 93)
  Index code 151.
- Laboratory of Nuclear Medicine and Radiation Biology. Audit., 1960-1961; 1968.; 1 folder. (Box 93)
- Marion Davies Foundation. Cherry, Gwynne Hazen, Memorial Laboratories., 1966-1968.; 1 folder. (Box 93)
  Index code 147.
- Recreation Center., 1965-1969. (Box 93)
  Index code 152.
- Reed Neurological Research Center., 1963-1970.; 1 folder. (Box 93)
  Index code 149.
- Survey Research Center., 1965-1966; 1968-1969. (Box 93)
  Index code 150.
- Water Resources., 1965-1967; 1970. (Box 93)
  Index code 153.
- Memorandum of Understanding Between NASA and Regents Concerning Research Facility Grant., 1963. (Box 94)
  Index code 154.
- NASA. Space Sciences Center., 1962-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 94)
- National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA)., 1958-1970. (Box 94)
- Proposal for Space Center at UCLA., 1962. (Box 94)
- African Studies, Center for., 1958-1970. (Box 95)
  Index code 155-Afr.
- Foreign Area Studies. Ford Foundation. SCAR (Statewide Committee on Area Studies)., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 95)
  Index code 155.
- Institute of International and Foreign Studies., 1958-1962. (Box 95)
- National Polytechnic Institute. UCLA Project., 1963-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 95)
- Overseas Programs., 1964-1970. (Box 95)
- CETREDE. Agreement Between Regents and Organization of American States., 1964-1967.; 1 folder (Box 96)
  Index code 155-Lat.
- Chile., 1969-1970. (Box 96)
  Index code 155-Chile.
- Comparative Folklore and Mythology., 1960-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 96)
  Index code 155-M.
- Geophysics, Institute of., 1958; 1960-1963; 1969-1970.; 4 folders (Box 96)
  Index code 156.
- James B. Duke Endowment for Russian Studies. Center for Russian and East European Studies., 1960-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 96)
- Latin American Studies Center., 1963-1970. (Box 96)
- Near Eastern Studies Center., 1963-1970. (Box 96)
  Index code 155-N.
- Russian and East European Studies, Center for., 1961; 1967. (Box 96)
  Index code 155-Rus.
- Business and Economics, Bureau of., 1960-1961. (Box 97)
  Index code 159.
- Institute of Industrial Relations., 1962-1969. (Box 97)
  Index code 158.
- Isotope Laboratory in the Institute of Geophysics., 1959-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 97)
- Numerical Analysis Research Program., 1949-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 97)
  Index code 157.
- Weather Control Research., 1958-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 97)
- Cancer Research., 1961. (Box 98)
  Index code 162.
- Dr. H. S. Penn Cancer Research., 1954-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 98)
- Folklore and Mythology Studies Center., 1963-1966. (Box 98)
- Government and Public Affairs, Institute of., 1960-1962; 1965-1967; 1970. (Box 98)
  Index code 160.
- Jules Stein Eye Institute., 1961-1963. (Box 98)
  Index code 163.
- Medieval and Renaissance Studies Center., 1968-1970. (Box 98)
- Neuropsychiatric Institute., 1960-1970. (Box 98)
  Index code 161.
- Neuropsychiatric Institute. Transfer of Neurosurgical Programs in NPI from Department of Mental Hygiene to UC., 1965-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 98)
- NPI Atomic Energy Project., 1954-1960. (Box 98)
- Nuclear Reactor for School of Engineering (Swimming Pool Type)., 1951-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 98)
  Index code 161-N.
- American Studies, Center for., 1965-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 99)
  Index code 164.
- Institute of Advanced Studies (von Neumann Memorial)., 1957-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 99)
- Institutes., 1965-1970. (Box 99)
- Miscellaneous Institutes of the Campus., 1960-1968. (Box 99)
- Policy on Institutes, Bureau's and other ORU's., 1957-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 99)
- Center for Computer-Based Behavioral Studies., 1970. (Box 100)
  Index code 164.5.
- Institute of Environmental and Evolutionary Biology., 1965-1970. (Box 100)
  Index code 164.3.
- Institutes Not Having Their Own Number., 1970. (Box 100)
- Latin American Studies Center., 1960-1962. (Box 100)
  Index code 165.
- Materials Institute., 1959-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 100)
- Materials Research Program Proposal by the Department of Chemistry., 1959-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 100)
- Navigation, Institute of., 1944-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 100)
- Proposed Institutes., 1970. (Box 100)
- Brain Research Institute., 1961-1970. (Box 101)
  Index code 168.
- Middle Eastern Studies (Cairo)., 1961-1962. (Box 101)
  Index code 167-M.
- Molecular Biology Institute., 1961-1970. (Box 101)
  Index code 167.
- Mountain Park Research Center., 1963-1968; 1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 101)
- Near Eastern Center., 1960-1962. (Box 101)
- Transportation and Traffic Engineering, Institute of., 1960; 1966-1969. (Box 101)
  Index code 166.
- UCLA - Columbia Project., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 101)
- Chief Campus Officers, Council of., 1959-1960. (Box 102)
  Index code 170.
- Council of Chancellors., 1960-1962. (Box 102)
- Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education., 1962-1970. (Box 102)
  Index code 169.
- Chief Campus Offcies, Council of., 1962-1969. (Box 103)
- Council of Chancllors., 1963-1966. (Box 103)
- Council of Chancellors., 1967-1969. (Box 104)
- Council of Chancellors., 1967-1970. (Box 105)